Dedicated Customer Service professional with knowledge of service delivery and proven multitasking abilities. Experience on resolving account and service concerns for customers. Smoothly uncovers and solves challenges while committed to maintaining professional relationships Focused on surpassing expectations and driving team success.

Work History

2020-08 – 2022-8

Customer Service Representative

Teleperformance, Santo Domingo, National District

- Maintaining customer satisfaction with forwardthinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns.
- Providing primary customer support to internal and external customers regarding their billing's health insurance and medical claims.
- Providing information regarding their health insurance benefits.

2019- 3-2020-09

Customer Service Representative

ERC International, Santo Domingo, National District

- Providing technical answers to customers.
- Using Specialized knowledge to provide customers personalized assistance.
- Friendly customer service offering excellent troubleshooting steps.
- Maintaining customers educated regarding their bills and payments.
- Eliminating customer service issues by quickly resolving disputes and correcting problems.

Warehouse worker

2022-09-

United Parcel Service, Caledon, Inglewood.

2022-09

 Responsible for loading, unloading, shipping, receiving, scanning, sorting, and stocking packages.

Education

2020-05 -

Mikael Burgos Vasquez

Contact

Address

KM 17 Auto Duarte , Santa Barbara #

Phone

829-263-7884

E-mail

Mikaelburgos1997@gmail.co m

Skills

Customer Service

Very Good

Report preparation

Excellent

Multi-line phone talent

Excellent

Technical Support

Very Good

Training development aptitude

Excellent

Stock management

Very Good

Software Development

current

ITLA – Instituto Tecnologico de Las Americas- Las Americas Highway, KM 27, La Caleta, calle 27, 11606

• Currently studying.

2015-06-2016-06

High School Diploma

– Eugenio Maria de Hostos Hight School, Los Alcarrizos, Santo Domingo

